Now let's add a Kotlin project new project to active calling name.
This is my area speed hotline select automotive here ISP quote quarterly activity the activity main
activity launcher finish.
Now let's add the Kotlin project to the Aosp, or this time we'll just copy my Aosp Java copy, paste
it here.
It's rename this to
my recipe.
Now let's copy the files and edit the CP file.
Let's first copy the source java comb folder.
Delete this one.
It could be.
Okay.
Now we
delete this first.
And now the manifest.
All right.
So now it's copied.
Let's come back to your code.
So now here we are in activity and my is p coding.
So here the only thing which we need to change is could include Katy here so that it will pick up the
code while also change the name of my aosp code and it should pick up the standard gate file.
So in case if you have both Java and Kotlin, you can just keep it like this java.
So both it will pick up both Kotlin and Java source files from the source directory and the resource
directory is these all will remain the same is fine.
So also fine.
So let's go ahead and add this module to the bottom case.
So let's add it here.
I had with them in.
So let's open them later.
So here we go.
My air speed is there.
We haven't added any text here.
That's why it's blank.